mostusefultricks.com 2016-11-01

# Privacy Policy – Most Useful Tricks

_**This is the Privacy Policy for www.mostusefultricks.com**_

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contacts by email at [sagarbasaksb@gmail.com](mailto:sagarbasaksb@gmail.com)  
At www.mostusefultricks.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.mostusefultricks.com and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.mostusefultricks.com don’t use any log files. But we do use Google analytics for knowing more about our audience. What you guys like to read, which articles are popular in this blog and etc.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.mostusefultricks.com does use cookies to store information about visitor’s preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Google AdSense Enabled Websites but currently We are not monetizing this site using Google AdSense.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Infolinks

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.mostusefultricks.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

_www.mostusefultricks.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers._

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.mostusefultricks.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.  
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
